the government shut down a new move to save thousands of jobs
for now it is October 16th this is today.
Overnight not so fast a federal judge temporarily blocking
president Trump from firing government workers during the
shutdown that emergency order coming just hours after the
White House said even more layoffs are on the way.
I think we'll probably end up being north of 10,000.
This is lawmakers on Capitol Hill look to a new strategy
on day 16 aimed at potentially ending the stalemate.
We'll have the very latest.
Major escalation president Trump revealing he's
now authorized the CIA to operate inside Venezuela.
We are certainly looking at land now because
we've got to see very well under control.
A controversial decision coming in the wake of U.S.
strikes on alleged drug boats from that country.
The details in a live report from the White House
plus the next American city now being targeted by
the president for another National Guard deployment.
Bouncing back leaders of the nation's top banks now
using the word resilient to describe the economy.
The head of Wal-Mart going even further calling it very strong
even as consumers face rising prices and the impact of tariffs.
So what does it all mean for your bottom line.
We'll break it down.
Hurtful and exhausting Britney Spears issued that new response
to troubling claims in her former husband's memoir where he voiced
concern for the music star's health and safety this morning.
Why Spears insists Kevin Federline is trying to cash in on lies and
what she wants the world to know about her relationship with her sons.
Capping discomfort the newly announced fee that is outraging
a lot of passengers one airline ready to charge you more for
a seat that reclines straight ahead just how much that extra
leg room will cost and how the airline is defending the move.
Those stories plus new details Diane Keaton's family revealing
the beloved Oscar winning stars cause of death their message to
fans and what we're learning about Keaton's health challenges
just ahead.
And talking turkey ready or not stores already launching
Thanksgiving deals 6 weeks before the big day where you can
gobble up the bargains in stock up for the holiday today
Thursday October 16th 2025.
From NBC News.
This is today with Savannah Guthrie and Greg Melvin
from studio one a in Rockefeller Plaza.
And a very good morning to welcome to today on this
Thursday morning so glad you decided to start with us.
Yeah,
nice to have you on with us several headlines breaking
this morning,
including Venezuela condemning the U.S.
overnight after multiple deadly strikes on alleged drug boats
from that country and it comes after president Trump confirmed
to reporters yesterday that he is authorized see I action
against the country today is day 16 of the government shut
down overnight a legal win for federal workers and judge has
temporarily blocked mass firings of some employees are also
watching what some say is good news for the economy,
big banks now using the word
resilient to describe its current climate
recovering all that for you this morning
to start with NBC's chief Capitol Hill
correspondent Ryan nobles Ryan good
morning.
It could good morning and that ruling
from a federal judge comes as the Trump
administration's budget director
predicted that more than 10,000 workers
could lose their jobs as a result of the
shutdown and today for the first time
since the government shut down the
Senate will take a slightly different
approach at getting things back open.
This morning,
a legal clash unfolding over jobs and the
government shut down a judge putting an immediate
stop to the administration's layoff plans
ruling the shutdown was not an excuse for widespread layoffs.
The San Francisco judge siding
with labor unions and criticizing the White
House for assuming the quote laws don't apply to
them anymore.
The Trump administration has said
Democrats forcing a shutdown has forced
them to layoff workers who are normally just put on unpaid leave
and yesterday Trump's budget
director predicted more firings to come.
You can grow higher.
I think we'll probably end
up being north of 10,000 Virginia senator Mark
Warner who represents thousands of federal
employees say they welcome the legal win.
But the longer the shutdown goes, the more
difficult it becomes.
We're living in this age of trauma already and so far they're holding
the line.
The president and Republicans now
pushing for some workers to be paid.
We'll
find out tomorrow whether the Democrats want
to proceed to the defense appropriations bill.
The Senate will vote on a bill to fund the Pentagon,
which would include making sure
members of the military get paid.
But even that is just the beginning of a long process.
Democrats have yet to commit to voting.
Yes. Will Democrats support that defense bill?
We have to see what they're going to put on the floor.
They haven't told us yet.
And even
if they do,
it would still need to pass the House,
meaning the shutdown is guaranteed to
continue into next week.
The president, following more cuts are coming.
The Democrats,
they don't
talk about this.
You know,
we're getting rid of programs that we didn't like.
Now the vote
on the Pentagon's budget is expected to happen sometime this morning.
The Senate will also
vote for the 10th time on the short term spending
bill that would immediately reopen the government.
But that is once again expected to fail.
Craig.
Ryan Noble starting us off there, Ryan.
Thank
you.
The other big story in Washington this morning,
the president's announcement that
he has authorized covert CIA action inside
Venezuela and suggested ground strikes could
be next.
NBC's Garrett Haig joins us from the White House with more on this.
Garrett,
good morning.
Savannah.
Good morning.
It really was stunning confirmation yesterday from the
president that he'd authorized this covert action,
bringing what had been secret U.S.
operations at least somewhat into the open.
Mr.
Trump's actions against Venezuela so far have been related
to his efforts to control immigration and the drug trade.
The same issues also fueling the law enforcement crackdown
he continues to pursue on the streets of major U.S.
cities.
This morning,
President Trump escalating his fight
on immigration and the drug trade,
both at home and abroad,
saying yesterday that he authorized the
CIA to take covert action in Venezuela,
a rare admission from
an American president.
I authorized me for two reasons really.
Number one,
they have emptied their prisons into the United
States and the other thing of drugs overnight.
Venezuela calling the move unprecedented
and a grave violation of international law.
Trump yesterday asked whether the CIA
could target Venezuela's president.
Does the CIA have authority to take out Maduro?
That's a ridiculous question for me to be given.
Not really a ridiculous question,
but wouldn't it be a ridiculous question for me to answer?
It comes after
weeks of military strikes on boats off the coast of
the South American country accused of smuggling drugs,
lawmakers objecting,
including some Republicans.
Is it too much to ask to know the names of those we
kill before we kill them to know what evidence exists
of their guilt?
The president also touting his domestic actions on
immigration and crime yesterday warning more American cities
could soon see a surge in federal law enforcement,
including San Francisco.
California's Democratic Governor Gavin Newsom
noting violent crime is down 22% in San
Francisco compared to last year.
Meanwhile,
there are protests against the existing federal
presence in some cities.
Dramatic surveillance video emerging of an ICE arrest in Chicago.
Homeland Security officials said they made an
arrest of an undocumented immigrant after a
vehicle and foot chase,
then confronted by what they say was a hostile crowd,
officers
deploying tear gas and arresting two teenagers.
DHS says they arrested a 15 year old who is
a US citizen for assault and say he
admitted to throwing eggs at the agents.
The teen's
attorney also issued a statement saying in
part quote a 15 year old American citizen
was effectively disappeared for five hours in Chicago.
This is not law enforcement.
Illinois's Democratic governor has criticized this whole incident,
but specifically ICE
for their tactics and questioned whether they
may have violated a court order with the use
of that tear gas.
So we likely haven't heard the last about that episode Savannah.
Can
we get back to Venezuela?
Garrett,
the president has now acknowledged CIA action inside that
country.
Did he say anything else about what kind
of action against Venezuela might come
next?
Well,
he's floated the idea of striking on
Venezuelan territory itself next saying
the sea is quote very well under control.
It's hard to overstate what a major escalation
that action would be against Venezuela against its president.
Huge questions being raised
about the legality and constitutionality of any such strike.
And on top of that,
lawmakers
briefed by the administration have also expressed
concerns about potential retaliation from
trafficking groups as well as the risk of civilian casualties.
Congressional sources say.
Savannah Garrett Hake at the White House.
Thank you.
Now to the fragile truce in the Middle East with
Israel accusing Hamas of violating the peace deal.
The group is now saying it has returned
the remains of all hostages it can reach.
Adding it will take time and special equipment to recover the rest.
NBC's chief foreign correspondent Richard
Richard Engel, joins us live from Jerusalem
with the very latest on this one.
Richard, good morning.
Good morning, Craig.
This was never going to be easy.
And now Israel is saying that Hamas must do more
to locate and hand over the bodies of hostages
still missing in Gaza.
But U.S.
officials say this ceasefire is still holding.
Amid the near total destruction in Gaza,
Hamas says it can't locate any more of the bodies
of the hostages it kidnapped in Israel,
saying it needs specialized digging equipment and
heavy machinery that it says Israel isn't allowing in.
Freed hostages say they were kept in deep tunnels,
some now collapsed and apparently
buried under buildings.
So far,
Hamas has handed over to the Red Cross at
least 10 remains out of the 28 deceased
hostages still in Gaza.
Israel isn't accepting that and says after DNA testing that one of
the bodies wasn't a hostage.
This morning,
Prime Minister Netanyahu's office saying,
we will spare no effort until we return all of the fallen hostages.
President Trump says
Hamas is searching.
Well,
they're looking for absolutely some of
those bodies have been in there a long time
and some of them are under rubble.
He added Hamas,
which has returned to the streets of Gaza,
must lay down its weapons or else they have to do it.
If they don't do it, we'll do it.
The dispute over remains is holding up much needed aid into Gaza.
In response to the delay,
Israel is only allowing in a small portion of the 600 trucks per day.
It's promised in President Trump's peace deal in Hanunis.
The Tawil family is now living in a tent,
just steps from their destroyed home.
Seven year old Jude used to have a Barbie and a play kitchen.
Now she makes mud cakes.
I'm just playing with sand because I have no toys.
I went to our house.
There was nothing left, she says,
as Israeli drones fly overhead.
As Israel still waits for the remains of more missing hostages,
some of those who were handed over have already been buried.
Craig,
our chief foreign correspondent
Richard Engelforce there in Jerusalem.
Richard,
thank you much more to get to this morning,
including positive signs when it comes to parts of the economy.
Some of the nation's biggest banks now reporting
strong earnings and the head of JP Morgan says,
despite uncertainty over the tariffs trade and the risk of inflation,
the economy has generally remained resilient.
So what does that mean for you and your bottom line,
NBC senior business correspondent,
Christine Romans here with those answers.
Resilience,
this is a word that the bank executives anyway
are using a lot to describe this economy.
It is the word of the moment and also the Walmart US CEO
saying the same thing,
saying that American consumer
has proven very resilient and that it's actually
a really strong economy overall.
Look,
you have really,
I think a once in a lifetime
investment in artificial intelligence
that's really kind of goosing the economy overall as well.
But there are a lot of things happening here
that would just keep defying gravity over and over again.
So the bank saying that American consumer continues to spend.
And in fact,
if you look at somebody who's got a job,
a house, and maybe some savings or a 401k,
that's where a lot of the spending is coming in the economy
because that part of the economy is doing very well.
The paycheck to paycheck customer,
a little bit more cautious, but again,
still spending, still resilient.
What about consumer confidence?
Yeah, that is the lowest we've seen since April.
And so we do know that there is kind of a sour mood
about affordability on main street.
And I think a big reason there is
because things just cost more still.
I mean, it's record high beef prices.
Grocery prices are still higher here.
In fact,
if you look at grocery prices in the CPI,
the consumer price index that we measure,
they're up about 17% from just 2022.
So that is,
I think,
the real feel indicated for most people.
You go to the grocery store,
the basket of groceries that used to cost 100
bucks a couple of years ago now cost $117.
That's real money.
And I think that's why you have kind of a sour mood.
But again,
these CEOs,
they have their thumb on the pulse of the American economy
and they see us out there still spending our money.
And that's really important.
I will just circle back to the AI thing.
It's hard to measure just exactly what AI is doing and how it might
be really lifting the overall economy and how long that lasts.
I was with the Treasury Secretary yesterday.
He told reporters he thinks he was asked if there's an AI bubble.
And he said he thinks that this is the third
inning inning of the AI spending spree.
And so we're just in the early phases
of how that's going to maybe transform.
And that's nine innings we're going with.
OK, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
Thank you.
Rescue efforts are still underway in Alaska this
morning following the weekend storm that brought
record water levels to two coastal villages there.
The Alaska National Guard airlifted some 300 people from the low
lying communities that were ravaged by high surf and strong winds.
The storm washed away several homes,
some with with people still inside.
At least one person was killed.
Two people are still missing there.
Officials say the remoteness of the area and the scale of the
destruction has created some challenges.
They say they're
making sure residents are safe and well cared for.
That's their
top priority.
All right.
Let us get our first check of the
weather.
Dylan's in for hours off for a couple days.
What's up,
Hightel?
Good morning, guys.
It is certainly much, much colder
out there across the Northeast.
In fact, we have frost
advisories, freeze watches, freeze warnings.
For us, it just
makes us feel cold.
But for plants, this could be the end of
the season for you folks dealing with
some of those really cold temperatures.
Thirty nine in Buffalo,
Saranac Lake,
30 degrees.
We had 29 earlier this morning,
Albany at 40,
Bridgeport,
Connecticut,
44.
Where's the warm air?
It's sitting right in the middle of this country.
This ridge in the jet stream has been bringing
in those temperatures that are near record highs.
We could in isolated cities break some records today.
Omaha,
82,
Oklahoma City,
83 degrees,
Pine Bluff,
87.
You go out west, though.
Jackson is only 46 degrees.
Vegas, 72. That's 10 degrees below average.
Tomorrow,
the heat continues through St. Louis,
through Memphis,
Detroit.
Sixty six degrees looks pretty good.
And then going into the weekend for the Northeast,
this could be the last really
warm weekend.
And by warm, I mean 69 degrees on Sunday.
That looks pretty good.
Monday, we drop back down to about 66.
Richmond in the 70s,
Pittsburgh in the 70s before we drop to 60 on Monday.
That's look at the weather across the country.
We'll get to your local forecast in the next 30 seconds.
I know I just was like getting into the 80s. I mean,
remember
that iconic scene from the 1982 classic,
An Officer and a
Gentleman and that gentleman is in the building.
Richard Gere right here.
We'll talk to him.
He's got an inspiring new project.
Yes. Just ahead.
Looks at his relationship with his mentor and friend,
the Dalai Lama.
Yeah, it's really cool.
He went to Indian Apollo.
That movie came out probably early 80s and
they've been friends for over 40 years.
I know.
A lot of wisdom there.
All right.
So we'll talk to him in a minute.
This gentleman is here for Pop Star.
Yes. First up though in this half hour,
an update on a story that we brought you yesterday.
Britney Spears
out with a new response to troubling claims being made
about her in an upcoming memoir from her former husband,
Kevin Federline.
NBC's Chloe Moloss is on the story again
with more on what Britney has to say now.
Chloe, good morning.
Hey guys.
Good morning.
Britney Spears is shedding more light on what she
calls a complex relationship with her two sons,
saying one has only seen her a handful of times in the last
five years and the other just once for only 45 minutes.
She says that they have always witnessed their father's lack of
respect for her and so far there are no signs of reconciling.
This morning,
Britney Spears firing back,
lashing out at what she calls constant
gaslighting from her former husband,
Kevin Federline,
after Federline made headlines with an upcoming
memoir accusing Spears of disturbing behavior.
The pop icon and former backup dancer
who shared two children divorced in 2007.
According to the New York Times,
Federline says he hasn't spoken to Spears in years
and learned about much of it from his children.
At one point,
Federline writing that their sons would quote,
awaken sometimes at night to find her standing
silently in the doorway watching them sleep.
Oh, you're awake with a knife in her hand.
Then she'd turn around and pat off without explanation.
I kind of have to sound the alarm.
I just wish that their mom would get help.
Now Spears writing.
I have always pleaded and screamed to have a life with my boys.
Relationships with teenage boys is complex.
She added that her sons who are 19 and 20 quote,
need to take responsibility for themselves.
According to the Times,
Federline also accusing Spears
of use of drugs and alcohol, an angry outburst
during the late stages of their marriage
and weighing in on her 13 year conservatorship,
which was highly publicized in documentaries
and the Free Britney movement.
Ended after an emotional court battle in 2021,
everybody deserves to be free, right?
But at what cost if it's at your own
demise or your own self destruction,
I mean,
is that really free Spears now urging fans
to ignore accounts of her mental health
I am actually a pretty intelligent woman who.
who has been trying to live a sacred and private life
the past five years.
Finishing,
I speak on this because I have had enough
and any real woman would do the same.
When asked about his decision to write this book now,
Kevin Federline says money is not at the root of his story
and it never has been.
Now Spears' team is refuting that,
saying that this all quote sadly comes after child support
has ended with Kevin.
All right.
Chloe,
thank you very much just that a closer look at the new
fee just announced by one airline that's getting a lot of
attention from passengers everywhere should you have to
pay more for a seat that recline next it will be like
the middle row armrest that to even get into this you take your
socks off guys also coming up.
Are you ready to buy a turkey and all the trimmings yet
will Brian chunks here with this year's very early start
Thanksgiving.
Hey good morning,
everyone,
it's not too early to
preheat your ovens already for Thanksgiving will explain why
shopping early could help you save a buck that on the other
side right here on today.
We're back 7.37 this morning in death today we're driving into
the countdown to Thanksgiving.
All right,
let's count it down 6 weeks away and that may seem
like a long time but at some stores,
they're already rolling
out deals for everybody for their big holiday feast.
NBC's business correspondent Brian Chung here to skip over
yet another.
Halloween's a few days away.
I'm done I'm done with that we're moving on
Halloween story in July I read that yeah,
yeah,
we'll be doing Christmas story soon,
but look with higher prices understandable
that some might have a little heartburn about
getting that turkey dinner together this year
with some early planning and a little creativity
there's still some savings to be thankful for.
Thanksgiving with no turkey is like like
4th of July with no apple pie.
It's never too early to start thinking about that grocery
bill for Thanksgiving
shoppers nationwide are already stocking up ahead of turkey
day here's a little PSA start getting
your dry ingredients and non perishables
with Aldi getting an early jump on
Thanksgiving prep announcing a $40 haul
that will feed
10 turkey side dishes and pie all included
that deal $7 cheaper
than it was last year.
Honey baked ham company also already selling a frozen
Thanksgiving dinner that can feed up
to 18 for less than $200 with all the
fixings these offerings hitting at a time
where inflation remains top of mind for
consumers.
I'm at the grocery store and these prices are ridiculous.
The cost of
turkey might also gobble up more out
of your wallet with news warnings of
economic factors and disease challenges
that could drive up prices about 40%
speaking of flavor Popeyes advertising a
$55 pre cooked Cajun turkey offering the
option to outsource the holiday bird
entirely while consumers are getting
creative to cut costs around the dinner table.
Whatever you would normally cook
through the weekday.
That's what we're gonna have.
It might be spaghetti.
According to a recent report,
21% of people saying they'll plan to ask guests
to bring part of the meal with 15%
saying they may swap side dishes to save
a buck.
Consumers are gonna get around higher costs by shopping for less.
They're going
to invite fewer people.
They're gonna have smaller portions.
It's not all bad news compared
to overall inflation.
Price increases haven't been as bad for staples like potatoes as well
as sauces and grates.
But of course,
snagging a good deal ahead of the holiday is the one
thing experts say consumers will be grateful
for during these really difficult economic
times kind of like going shopping for Thanksgiving airfare.
You're not going to wait until that last
week and expect to get a great deal.
So we know there are a lot of these these meal deals out there.
But what if you actually like cooking
and you want to save on the groceries
themselves.
Yeah.
Well look I mean beyond shopping early there are some strategies
like for example using frozen vegetables for stuffing.
It's just as
fresh and honestly it's probably a lot cheaper as well.
And then when it comes to making pie
if you just make the crust yourself as
opposed to buy store bought you're going to save a lot of money.
I mean it isn't only like three ingredients butter flour water sugar.
And then lastly
offer store brands over over names.
I think that a lot of times you want to go with the big.
Yeah.
You know and actually it was a Wells Fargo
report that suggested if you buy the name brands
it's going to cost about 90 bucks whereas it
will be seventy three dollars if you just buy the
generics which means that you could get seventeen dollars
in savings depending on what your basket Thanksgiving.
I love Thanksgiving.
You just
have to sit there and eat yeah,
yeah,
you're with your friends
family watch some football,
although as a Jets fan,
it's
always painful.
But it is why is texted to preheat the oven.
Thanks.
All right.
I turned to another check of the weather
dealing with the Thanksgiving forecast.
I did already 2027
of cranberry sauce,
it's good jelly cranberry sauce just in
case they sell out.
We've got some quiet weather across the
country except for this one spot the storm system that's
moving out of the Rockies into areas like North and South Dakota.
We are seeing the clouds there Casper
Wyoming seeing some clouds and some showers,
the higher elevations getting in on some snow there too.
This is going to continue to move eastward and you
can see this line out ahead of this cold front as
this moves to the east by the time we get to Friday.
We are going to see this start to trigger
some storms through parts of the Midwest.
So just something to keep an eye out for and we do have the chance,
especially on Saturday seeing these continue
to move out of Iowa through Illinois through
Missouri where we could see some of those stronger
storms hail and wind would be our biggest threats here,
especially in this area in orange that does even stretch down into
Arkansas in the parts of northern Louisiana wind gusts up to about 60
miles per hour a possibility and a few tornadoes possible not likely
but possible today though it is that heavy rain across eastern Montana
up across North Dakota sunny and warm down South cool in the Northeast
temperatures dropping down into the 50's with that cool breeze.
It'll make it feel even chillier.
That's look at the weather across the country.
Now here's a peek out your window.
Yeah,
that's your latest forecast surprise you by
cranberries so she's the type that would need a good can of
ocean spray can cranberries.
Just the good stuff that flops
on a plate and slice it with a butter knife,
it's so great man
you're talking like that's appetizing.
The tone of your
voice like so good.
All right,
I'm guy right about I'm not I'm not a man and I
maybe it's the way you prepare.
Yeah, what is my wife.
Odds are you're right.
Yeah, let's get to our PSS P this
morning,
a good sneak peek legendary comedian Jim carries
and talks for his next big role,
a live action remake of this
futuristic family.
I mean you have to have a wrap your head around this whole
thing but he'd be perfect for George Jetson live action remake
the 60 year-old cartoon.
We don't know a ton about the
movie there's a director attached that we know that so
there's so there's that I mean you got Jim Kerry who's known
he's multi generationally loved.
Yeah, what he did for
Sonic the hedgehog and for the Grinch you can see that if
George Jetson goes a little dark he can cover that how about
this is Jane Jetson the wife,
okay,
my suggestion is mine
okay, Elizabeth banks.
Yeah, she would be great, you know,
I thought of that and Christina Hendricks her madman.
And just kind of like retro and 60's and cool love the job
Katherine Han.
Oh she be good for Jane what about.
I don't have anybody
frowl Roy,
but we've got 2 great boost for you this morning
highlighting some adorable new additions that zoos across the
country first these messages.
Well back to us here she's brought a booth,
you know what
a buckle up because we've got a double scoop of good because
what's better than one cute animal video to start your day
how about to it's a big week for zoo debuts starting with
Cecil Cecil Cecil.
So like so I call him.
26 year-old I call him to see.
He's suddenly into his new home at the San Francisco.
He looks
friendly and is set to be introduced to the public this
weekend to keep an eye out.
He didn't like it that I called
him set up a French over new day in New Mexico,
the Albuquerque
bio Park Zoo is welcoming a precious new resident of their
own a baby hit.
Well, people say he's distracted by Craig
Craig cannot stop.
Yeah,
all right.
That's all is an
acceptable.
I do get back to a different place just don't think
that girl is the so what do you think it is so did they know
about the hippos pregnancy.
They didn't thank you for asking
the keeper said they did know about it,
but apparently the
calf's arrival was unplanned wait what I know that doesn't
make any sense.
Well, okay, I guess they did they know about
it.
Happy accident when a mommy.
Confirmation it's the soul.
Tomato tomato do you want to know what these hippos.
Karen and Mo it's actually.
I don't you love a name like
Karen for a hit by sure do you know reclaim that name yeah,
we've got to take care and back take care and back.
You've come
apart.
You're so sweaty.
I see because of that we're already.
Listening.
The tears that made me feel all the way you're switching up
day look kind of slimy.
What's coming up.
Guys coming up for the show House arena
carpenter is here enough for her big weekend on SNL she'll
take over both host and musical.
Hollywood legend Richard Gere live in our studio he hasn't
taken a big U turn said I would.
Yeah, anyway.
It's 8 o'clock on today coming up shut down showdown a federal
judge temporarily stopping president Trump from firing
thousands of government workers as the shutdown enters its 16th
day.
We're live in Washington with the next steps.
The only on me one airline now charging passengers of the
first seats that recline straight ahead the reaction is
causing just how much that extra comfortable cost.
And new details Dan Keaton's family now revealing the stars
cause of death.
The latest just ahead is new tributes for the
Hollywood legend poor it.
All that plus Richard Gere live in studio one a people are
looking at me.
I look at me.
Mariska and Kelly break it down.
And Sabrina getting ready for SNL.
He's really not excited for the weekend.
Sorry, I prefer a
strong and it's all ahead today Thursday October 16 2025.
Celebrate.
Yeah.
Good job teach.
Last.
Yes you're missing you should
the wine go back to watch it.
But we do have a lot to get to
in this hour going to start with your news at 8. We're going
to start with some breaking news here federal judge
temporarily blocking the Trump administration from firing
government workers during the ongoing shutdown the order
issued just hours after the White House said even more
layoffs are coming.
And we see chief Capitol correspondent Ryan nobles is in
Washington at his post with the very latest trying good morning.
Hey Craig good morning.
This is a temporary ruling that the
Trump administration is likely to appeal.
But the San Francisco based judge made it clear that she
believes the law does not allow the administration to use the
shutdown as an excuse to fire thousands of federal workers.
Now the ruling comes on the same day the White
House warned that more layoffs and cuts are coming.
The budget director predicting the job losses would
be quote north of 10. Thousand and President Trump
is also doubling down blaming Democrats and warning
it would they would come after a program
they support eventually as the shutdown continues.
The Democrats they don't talk about this.
You know we're getting rid of programs that we didn't like
but that were negotiated in but we didn't like with terminating those
programs and they're going to be terminated on a permanent basis.
Meanwhile today the Senate will attempt to pass a
bill that would authorize the Pentagon's budget.
Now if it passes it would still need the support
of the House but it would be a small step toward
making sure that military service members get paid.
They will also vote for the 10th time on the short term
spending bill that would immediately reopen the government.
But it is once again expected to fail.
Craig Ryan nobles there in Washington.
Ryan thank you.
A popular airline announced this week it is going to be a
long term plan.
It's going to start charging passengers
more money just to recline in their seats.
And as you can imagine people have thoughts about it.
Emily kind of joins us with the details.
Hey Emily good morning.
Good morning to you guys.
We've covered the controversy over whether
you should recline your seat on a flight.
But now WestJet is reconfiguring some of its
planes so that won't even be up for debate.
The Canadian airline says fixed upright seats and standard
economy are about preserving personal space while critics
are calling it the latest cash grab in the industry.
Sitting back and relaxing on a flight.
Enjoy famous town American clipper comfort.
Is going to start to cost you on one airline.
WestJet which serves 17 U.S.
states says it is getting rid of reclining seats
and standard economy on its newly remodeled planes.
The Canadian airline says fixed recline
will help preserve personal space.
Adding in a statement our refreshed cabin caters to our guests
diverse preferences whether they opt for premium seating with extra
amenities and leg room or for more
affordable ticket prices with less space.
Its new Boeing 737 will offer a three tiered
cabin layout according to WestJet with a new
premium cabin that will cost more but
provide a more comfortable seating angle.
The announcement prompting swift backlash from some frequent flyers.
I'm
really frustrated by the nickel and diming of
Americans including Clint Henderson from the points guy
who doesn't like it but acknowledges it's a smart
business move.
They know that they can sell those really cheaply
undercut the competition and then they're adding what's
basically a first class cabin on some of these planes.
They can sell those seats for more money.
If it's an overnight flight why you
wouldn't be allowed to recline your chair.
To recline or not to recline.
The ambiguous airplane etiquette has been the
cause of many heated confrontations but some say
WestJet's new change could solve that problem.
With one user commenting on X most flights are less
than five hours so you don't need to recline
while another writing yet another way to make
economy class more undesirable.
All of it coming at a time when airlines are already
charging more for assigned seats and extra leg room to checked bags.
You have lost two
loyal customers.
You will get charged $200 if your checked bag exceeds 62 inches.
So
could upright seats be flying to your favorite airline next.
I'm sure they're watching this
very closely and if WestJet is successful
in this I think it could spread to U.S.
carriers.
So WestJet's first reconfigured plane is expected to be in service
this month it says other changes include new seats back support
adjustable headrests and upgraded Wi-Fi you better hope for some pretty
impressive adjustable headrests if you can't we have passengers.
There's fees everywhere nowadays.
Yeah I'm the armrest the middle armrest is going to come next.
I mean yeah standing room only on the flight.
Yeah, it's all worked up and yes, thank you.
Baseball we go
to Toronto Blue Jays making a big statement last night that
the ALCS far from over.
A lot of their grow junior there with a solo shot the
fifth inning giving Toronto a 5 run lead they would go on to
beat the Mariners.
13 to 4.
Yeah still leads that series 2 games to one game for is tonight.
What I had in pop start Carson.
Well guys I'm actually confused,
I'm not sure how this item got
here says we're going to have highlights from last night's
victorious show.
Okay,
familiar, but of course to our
due diligence and dive right in on that including the performance
from Missy Elliott that stole the night.
Thank you for your commitment to research Carson,
thank you but
first talk about Diane Keaton her family has now revealed what
caused her death we're going to hear from them right after
this.
We're back at 8.11 now with some details on the sudden death
of beloved actress Diane Keaton now with tribute still pouring
in of course we're now hearing from her family and we see
Stephanie gots joins us with the latest after morning stuff
hey guys good morning.
Diane Keaton's family first
announced the legendary star's death on Saturday Keaton was 79
years old but still working her last film summer camp released last
Keaton's family is explaining what
led to her passing.
This morning after Diane Keaton's death shocked Hollywood.
The cause of death for the legendary
actress is coming to light.
In a statement shared exclusively with people Keaton's family
revealing that the star who was 79
years old passed away from pneumonia.
Adding they're
very grateful for the extraordinary messages
of love and support they have received these
past few days.
The Oscar winner had been a fixture on the screen for decades.
Oh well
la di da la di da la la.
Still making movies into her seventies but mostly out of the public
eye recently.
Still her death came as a surprise to her many fans.
Her family not revealing
more about Keaton's illness.
But Keaton's friend songwriter Carole Bayer Sager recently reflecting
on her last visit with the actress in an exclusive interview with
people saying I saw her two or three weeks ago and she was very thin.
She had lost so much weight adding I was kind of stunned.
Since Keaton's death over the weekend tributes have
been pouring in honoring the Oscar winning actress.
Filmmaker Nancy Myers also honoring her longtime friend and
frequent collaborator calling her fearless and born to be a
movie star.
Adding as a filmmaker I've lost a connection
with an actress that one can only dream of.
And her something's got to give co-star
Keanu Reeves honoring the Hollywood legend.
Such a unique extraordinary artist and person.
I had the chance to work with her once
and really cherish that experience.
Keaton's family also asked that any donations be made in her memory to
local food banks or animal shelters causes she was passionate about.
Stephanie thank you so much.
We want to turn to NBC News medical contributor Dr. Natalie Azar.
Pneumonia for certain age groups certain subsets of the community.
This is a very dangerous illness and obviously was for Diane Keaton.
It can be.
So pneumonia is an infection of the lung.
It can be caused by a number of different
bugs bacteria viruses even fungus.
Bacterial pneumonia is the most common type
of pneumonia and you know very treatable.
Many of us can be treated as outpatients.
We don't need to be hospitalized but it can be deadly.
There are about forty one
thousand deaths every year in this country and about a little
over a million emergency room visits because of pneumonia.
And as you
mentioned Savannah we always talk about the groups
that are potentially you know most vulnerable.
So we talk about infants and
people over the age of 65 weakened immune systems people with
underlying chronic illnesses can sometimes succumb to pneumonia.
I mean in terms of Diane Keaton obviously we don't we're not
familiar with her specific case.
So elderly older people are
more susceptible.
Yes and other other risk factors as well.
Well,
yes,
so we talk about of course being older and and and
having underlying medical conditions or or you know being
immunocompromised let's say and you know we don't know what
type of pneumonia she had you know we always sometimes we'll
talk about you know walking pneumonia
which is the name is a euphemism.
It's not really a medical term which means that
you can you can be walking around with pneumonia
and then suddenly it can turn very serious.
There are so many different types of pneumonia of course.
And you know just to remind everybody that the the
symptoms the things that you want to look out for right.
If you are feeling sick if you have bluish lips or blue
fingertips I know that sounds kind of worrisome to people
shortness of breath chest pain when you take a deep breath.
In confusion high fever a severe what we
call a wet cough or a productive cough.
But I'd like to take the opportunity to remind
people how we can maybe prevent pneumonia.
There are not vaccines for every type of pneumonia
but there are vaccines for RSV for covid and for flu.
Those are viral infections that can turn into pneumonia.
And also the pneumococcal vaccine.
This is really important.
Strep pneumonia is one of the most
serious types of bacterial pneumonia.
Just recently in the last year,
the CDC actually lowered the
recommended age to get the pneumococcal vaccine from 65 to
50 and just to remind everybody again no smoking.
You know get
all get all your vaccines to maintain a healthy lifestyle all
of those things can help prevent pneumonia as well.
All right good reminders Natalie sorry,
thank you so much
doctor,
it's and don't forget you can also find us on today's
show radio Syria, 6, and channel one.
All right as Mister Roker would say all right that's time of
the morning.
Well, we're going to do it guys first steps
rena carpenter the Grammy winner taking over studio 8 H
this weekend pulling double duty is both the host and musical
guests on Saturday night live but in a new promo she seems to
be lost in Kerry Bradshaw's world of sex in the city.
Sabrina what are you up to in these heels probably like 5,
4, he's very excited for the weekend.
Sorry, I prefer a
strong and
thank God, it's Mister big.
It's actually Marcelo but I'll take it okay,
hey,
so bring it
out a question about the pumpkin patch gas here anything
for a fan know I'm a writer.
The woman wondered what she'd gotten herself into having won
over the cast and crew.
The only thing left to do was what
she ready.
I did the computers not even on
what she's going to be great
by the way you know there's been over 900 episodes of Saturday
night live really less than 50 of them had somebody pulled
double duty.
But most and musical opening sequence when
they say hosted by a carpenter yes,
but I bring a car on our
scene to great at that next summer's car get a recently the
law and order theme song took over tiktok is fans of the show
dancing to that iconic theme on yesterday's episode,
the Kelly
Clarkson show.
Mishka hard to say and Kelly got a lesson from the master the
dance creator Stefan Vaughn van.
And then.
Wow I did not see that happen,
I did not dance that theme song
the law and order.
Yeah, they are yeah, it's going to get
younger viewers and trend it's hard for some of the keeper
concentration right now.
Yeah, because Mister years are.
Yeah.
everything,
I can't
believe well I have to catch a flight where you're going I'm
going to choose on Arizona, my hometown why.
I'm sure later on the show.
We haven't seen.
Yes.
Come over and sit with her for a second.
He's for 2 saw.
Town.
The great documentary though.
I know.
Add for Phoenix,
yes,
you're going to choose on why.
I've never been to sun.
I know.
Yeah,
I just got this but we have to switch gears.
I heard there was some sort of show last night.
Maybe you knew
about this models on the runway.
I don't know it didn't
catch my eye,
but I want to focus on the music that was absolutely incredible.
The
show stopper herself my friend miss.
Look to you rolling stone recently ranked
the turn 50 greatest songs of the 21st
century so far get your freak on the was number one that was
the name of the book about the dollar law might.
I think that
was but it's a song now so well you're here to keep.
The next interview that cmt a group of fans prank the music
superstar poking fun at his likeness to another big name in
country music Mister Blake Shelton.
You know he is still behind you though on the
number one count that's the only reason I'm
still in the game of country music.
It's a stay ahead and he thought he was retiring
and he's back putting songs out it's not the deal we had.
I look like the kind of it's a guy.
Finally we're going to end with Lee Manuel Miranda this week,
the Emmy Grammy and Tony winner surprise commuters at New York's
Grand Central station playing piano and some of his greatest
hits including in control from that we don't talk about Bruno.
It's not brought the piano.
He put up a performance is part
of a.
There's a call.
New York over and over and over again you left you talk about
Bruno a lot that's always yes,
that was a moment.
3, 4, years
ago, yeah, it was yeah, but the pandemic.
Really.
Well this is a good rehearsal,
I just hope we do it
live.
We all know our part to Richard.
I don't know.
I'm feeling like maybe a couple more days of her and I'll come
back on Monday.
Come with me and apologize.
I sent my parents
to Tucson once many.
And I would give them.
Every year give them a wonderful trip I first started
making money.
Yes, I give my parents these trips and great
trips.
We ran out of trips in Europe.
So ranch yeah to some yeah,
I know exactly what my mother
didn't ride.
But my father did my father grew up on a farm.
Okay, writer.
Well, I think the Paris of the West.
Only to side that's just ahead.
We're going to have much more
with this guy right here the one I'm leaving.
He said his parents on these trips and the wisdom of
happiness that you're sharing this amazing that your friend
and mentor the Dalai Lama after local.
And that's your latest forecast back inside you guys.
And for treat our joined by our unexpected pop star friend who
also happens to be a Hollywood legend Mister Richard gear.
Yes,
the award-winning star has charmed audiences for decades
with unforgettable performances like an officer in a gentleman
Chicago course pretty woman.
Well now he's taking his many
talents behind the camera new documentary is called the
wisdom of happiness.
It shares insights from his long-time
teacher and friend the Dalai Lama insights on how to find
peace and chaos and the importance of compassion to
cool.
If you have
more serious practice of a passion.
That's the ultimate sauce for peace of mind.
According my own experience.
Training of mind.
It's the key factor for happy life.
I'm sure good morning,
it's a morning it's to see you get to
see you it's beautiful my old friends,
I know I'm really
upset because she hasn't seen the film.
I haven't and she's
going to but she's also leaving for 2 songs as we talk about
those minutes ago.
Yes, so but anyhow we're going to talk about
the let's focus on the reason that you're here it's not a
documentary want to make that we're talking about is a
documentary it's not really a documentary because it's it's
kind of a hybrid.
Just one of the things I like it so much and proud of it but it's it.
It's bringing together this man's life.
This is his 90th year and July we just celebrated
90th year of this extraordinary life so part of this
is it is a doc about who he is where he came from.
But the strongest part of it and with lots
of archival footage when he was a child.
Yes. And in the 30s and 40s.
And 50's and went into exile because of the
Chinese invasion 1950 finally he's escaped in 1959,
but really
the core of this is is him teaching and his perspective of why this
world is so crazy that we're in right now and how to get out of it.
It's such a gift in that way to be able to hear his
teaching something that you have had the opportunity to.
To have for decades.
Blessed 45 years.
Did you have to convince him to do this or how did you say this came
to me there were Swiss filmmakers who are making this and one of them
was a still photographer that been around his Holiness for decades.
I've known him a long time.
Manuel Bauer and the wonderful photographer and.
So they started making this I'm always skeptical of
people making movies about his Holiness because sometimes
they don't really understand where he's coming from.
They're highly motivated but maybe they're not the best filmmakers.
And so they had this footage this extraordinary footage of his Holiness
looking right into the camera and which is it's kind of thrilling.
If it's like you're having a private audience with this
extraordinary man and they had used this technique that are
Morris who is a documentary film.
Yes.
Had pioneered where he puts a mirror in front of the lens of
that was wondering how he had so he's actually talking to
someone over here.
And that's why he's so engaged because
he's looking right into their eyes.
So it's a technique.
It's a technique that one on one now so anyone seeing this
movie you feel like you were I do side of him.
It's quite it's beyond revealing.
The one one thing and I've said this before another interview
but you saw this probably on your computer or a did.
Yeah.
Well it's OK. You're still going to get a hit from this.
We've screened this all over Europe.
It's just opening here now.
But to be in an audience with 100 200 300 strangers
with a big screen and feeling this at
the end of an hour and a half with his
tone is the Dalai Lama the atmosphere of the room radically changes.
And I've seen the lights come up and people start to
look at each other genuinely like brothers and sisters.
And you see well this right now this can change our world.
When they started making this film when
I got involved a year and a half ago
I thought it was the 90th year of the Dalai Lama is coming up.
This is a great testament and celebration of him.
But I think we all realize how the world is so radically
changed in the last year and a half.
We've all kind of fallen off a cliff.
And I'm hoping that this is some kind of a corrective that this is
a medicine of some kind that maybe can help us rethink where we're
at and how to get out of it before we let you get out of here.
Your dear friend Diane Keaton.
Yeah.
You work together on a number of films.
But one of my early films Looking for Mr. Goodbar was with her.
It was the second film I made was with her.
And obviously I think about her now.
We made a film a few years ago too.
I hadn't seen her in a long time.
She was.
That was a difficult film.
It was very kind of raw sexual film.
And
she's she's pretty shy and skittish.
I was too.
It was my second film.
And we kind of took care of each other
getting through these kind of challenging
physical scenes with each other.
But I remember just how sweet and gentle she was and how real.
And I think anyone who's ever worked with her just like this.
This is a real person.
A real original as well.
Completely original.
Richard Garrett thank you for being here.
Thank you.
I was just for you stuck around.
Put off the flight
to Tucson.
The flight was delayed.
We won't name the
airline.
But you know what?
I have now something to watch on
the flight.
Yes, you do.
And I very much look forward to it.
Well call me afterwards.
Let's make sure she had.
We don't have
her numbers.
No, we don't.
We'll give her the number because I
want to hear what you have to say.
Okay.
I really am looking
forward to it.
I hope everybody checks it out because.
We'll try
to see if you can see it.
It'll be online in all Latin.
Yeah, theater.
Yeah, because this this is something that can
radically change how we feel about each other.
Yeah, I agree
with you haven't seen it.
I agree with you doing things
together and look at each other in the eye and being in real
life is what we all need right now.
So thanks for being part
of that.
We're so happy.
This is in theaters tomorrow.
All
right coming up next.
We've got a special fall essentials
edition.
Don't leave Richard Geer hanging.
First this is today on NBC.
It is filled with essential items up to 84% off help you
settle in the season and comfort style and Joe Martin
is here today lifestyle and commerce contributor you can
always shop along with us to scan the handy dandy qr code
you see on your screen.
Joe good morning.
You look so cozy
and cute.
I love a chilly environment.
I know and we're starting with these fabulous jackets.
I'm so excited.
This was actually the brand when I was younger
that I could afford my first like expensive jacket.
Yeah,
I'm so excited to bring this laundry by Shelly Siegel Cole.
I love
laundry.
They're retail 150 to 350 in the deal price 45 to 69
that's up to 78% off their machine washable extra small to
extra large for reference.
I'm in the small crop and I just
want to show on this one that you can adjust it.
Okay, and it
has a sharp a hood which you know, I love
and then you it's
a puppy coat that gives you a waist not to to puff up.
Yeah, it has this built in bed.
So this is the proper version
in all the different colors.
Then you have the crop version
which has the sharp a hood there and then you this is fully
lined in sharp and all different colors and look at these
colors.
I mean we have some shots here of all the different
colors of how to wear it but really great again in extra
small to large.
Amazing okay.
This is a triumph and our biggest deal of the day.
This is
Cody cash wear scarf in your gloves retail to 40 deal price
3984% off the hat is one size fits most I happen to have a
7 and 3 quarters head which is and it fits me perfectly don't
worry about it.
Thank you I think that my acid washed in I
know I needed this big deal because you got Richard Gere's
digits, it's hard to.
Yeah, you are so I'm coming up with cash
yeah,
you get the gloves hot or scarf you can split them up as
a great gift or put them in the set again $39 84% off and all
the colors.
All right here you go what is there welcome hand
warmers oh my gosh they're not only hand warmers that are
dribble so the fuel elect electric hand warmer set of 2
up to a 130 degrees they do they were chargeable and
reusable deal prices $29 it's a set of 2 yeah,
59% off you
cannot go wrong with the nice putting on the back of my neck.
Good so OK this is the tea's tea smart heated mug and charger
bundle the retail one 37 the deal price 5957% off and free
shipping on orders over $60 what's wonderful about this it
comes with the tea then you make the tea then it keeps it hot
on this warmer for 6 hours,
but then there's more it also works
as a charger know your phone charger.
You make tea I often
forget about it because it's hot and then you wait for it
cold years, your solution.
What a beautiful gas.
Look there's
a random bird okay.
That's okay so the over appliance rapid rice cooker now
our chefs in the kitchen said this is amazing it does more
than rice and make soups mac and cheese for Todd is banana
bread you just put it in you click the button and then when
it's done it will click and the rice will be ready I like it.
I think it's because I mean it's how much rice can you make
it but now our producer soups mac and cheese egg for Todd is banana
bread so small that every make a huge crock pot or something
right and then you can put it underneath for storage and last
stop now that we're going to be inside I love myself an air
purifier especially that dispenses sent in the
appropriate amount so one 4999 deal price $59 61% off the
brand says it has a 3 layer filtration system that can
remove 99.97% of air pollutants like smoke and odors so
you can get the essential oil separately but you put it in this
little spot here and then he is here I work.
Any day so that's
using their brand but I will check on any and put my
instagram if you could use another okay just asking we have
the products on more time yes of course so we have the laundry
by Shelley Segal coats the my boat 40 cashmere collection,
the fuel electronic hair and warmers the tea's tea smart
heated.
This mark he did okay,
T the meco smart air purifier
with diffuser and now we have more okay don't we want to get
the deals just go to today dot com slash chill you do have
a special price.
I do before we go so one lucky person will
leave the Plaza empty handed thanks to our Wells Fargo active
cash credit card sponsor get out of the way so I see a bird
everybody.
I heard it's your birthday.
You look fabulous tell me your name and
where you're from Julie from Danville
California is this the best birthday
ever best birthday ever said thank you
it's about to be better because we are giving you all the steals and.
Happy birthday.
So much.
Julie.
Carson.
So chef from Georgia
heavy plate Augusta national yet or not.
You get me on you know anybody that we're going to work on
that guys we have some good Southern cooking coming up for
your family will feed yourself great meatloaf dish with miss
Hannah Taylor's beloved family recipe,
but the cookbook talk
about and a road trip at first this is today on NBC.
I was just explaining your cooking skills and how how good
they are this morning on today's food.
We're cooking up
some so we got a house everybody millions of you know
her as the lily Lou Tay and she's out the very first cookbook
comes out in a couple days called measure your heart
Southern home cooking to feed your family and so I love the
story about your mom who had recipes on cards and how about
explain the flower kiss remember me that was my grandmother's so
when I was very little she would you're going to cry.
cars you be making biscuits with him.
Yes, and she would as a
fun little thing she would flow flower at like a flower kiss.
I mean I love that would go everywhere.
Your whole book
feels like that so you took a road trip up from Georgia,
you got your 3 kids you left the dogs,
the cats and the
chickens idea we got James Taylor your man with you not
that James Taylor,
but you're your and who's in a lot of your
your videos and they're here in New York and you're going to
go to this book tour.
Yeah, well that's why that's a reality
show.
Yeah,
all right so what we do what you make it is
grandma's meat loss.
So we're making Mary's meatloaf today.
This is should be served for Thanksgiving.
Instead of Turkey.
I agree thank you.
The whole thing is cooking with love not
precision.
There's like that's the point of this love that
perfect.
We're just going to chop up some peppers.
Yeah,
and yeah,
so the first thing goes down is just what yeah
peppers all of the all right on you have green pepper and garlic
in there too.
Yeah, and sauteed for about 3 to 5 minutes.
Okay, okay.
Yep and so once that's cooked we're going to
move over to the egg and bread crumbs okay,
okay,
so what we're
going to do is just dump that right in there and we're going
to start up you know and we're going to let it sit so these
bread crumbs will soften like how long like a no just a few
minutes,
okay,
they'll soften pretty quick so right so we'll
just let them set in soft and I work on this what kind of what
kind of meat was in
his meal.
So I use she used the yeah,
but when I started cooking at home,
I incorporated pork so I
do a mixture of both 50 50 okay,
so once those soft and
we're just going to dump our sauteed veggies that's like
8020 ground beef right a little bit of content.
Absolutely
and you were sent pork yeah,
yeah,
and then we've got a lot
of parsley.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, so just our we're
going to dump them in there and then we have our seasonings now
let me tell you this tell me it's a secret ingredient.
Okay, honey.
I did you taste a little bit that we really let me take
another take another bite,
but you don't really want this meat
love to be sweet,
but it adds a nice little something it does with
the kind of that sweet and savory you get that yeah,
I do get that yeah,
so we're just going to dump that was our kind
and our our paper that was all purpose and then
just some tomato tomato paste tomato paste yeah,
what's that.
Lemon lemon zest sorry yeah,
and then we're just going to mix
that all together and form beautiful.
Yeah, you find out
cooking out for you just pop that our now,
but I'd let it see
it because you don't want to burn your mouth is real easy to
dig in and burn your mouth so let me see it okay.
And this is
just a quick gravy, you know cream.
Yeah, okay.
Great so our butternut squash casserole this pair perfectly
with the meat love yeah, and so
you know scoop your seeds out
of your squash chop it up you can use a mandolin.
Oh that is yeah,
and then you make your cream sauce right
here to go over you put your cream sauce in and then you top
it with cheese that is ridiculously good.
Yeah, 10 full
40 minutes in the oven take the temple off let it Brown and
then you're good to go.
The question husband in the book
you can do a book tour here with yes,
but and you're driving
all over the country pretty.
I love.
Yeah, we're in says
cook you just taste the love in your food.
Yeah, please.
Delicious measure with your heart cookbook out next week you
find the recipes at state dot com slash food.
The family
for us.
One tip she said she makes a meatloaf that shows a part of
all the part.
The a maybe the next minute maybe need to do more eggs,
I don't think I do it.
Okay, maybe more low and slow on the
cook.
Look at Hannah and her.
I love it.
DIY projects to get
your home ready for the cold months.
All right 4th hour
Jenna celebrating reading rainbow.
Hey thanks for watching don't forget you can catch the today show
every morning on NBC or take today when you're on the go just follow
the today podcast on Apple podcast spotify or wherever you listen.